<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>m4ftm</title>
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm" />
    <updated>2019-09-17T18:56:48-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>ItsExtra</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Beta Site Feedback</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/beta-feedback/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/beta-feedback/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:21:08-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This website is being circulated within trans male communities for feedback before "launching". Public launch is anticipated for late 2019 or early 2020. Email: m4ftm@protonmail.com Twitter: @m4ftm
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0d5ukb0">This website is being circulated within trans male communities for feedback before "launching". Public launch is anticipated for late 2019 or early 2020. </p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0lsuha0">Feedback is being sought and acted upon (even if you do not ID as a trans man). I will respond by your preferred method of contact if provided. Here are a few questions to get you thinking:</h2>
<ul>
<li>What do you think of the concept of this site?</li>
<li>How accurate and inclusive is the information provided?</li>
<li>What is missing? What sections should be expanded?</li>
<li>What do you think of the tone and style of the site?</li>
<li>Is there anyone you would recommend as a contributor, collaborator or to whom I should otherwise reach out?</li>
<li>Were there any technical or design aspects you had trouble with? Is it easy to find what you want?</li>
<li>How well does it convey the required information to the target audience?</li>
<li>Is the language understandable? Did I let any jargon slip in without explaining it?</li>
<li>If you are a cis man, does it make you feel any different about trans men?</li>
<li>If you are a trans man, would you share this with a cis guy you wanted to fuck? What could make it more helpful?</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0lt2mn1">Contact</h2>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:m4ftm@protonmail.com">m4ftm@protonmail.com</a> </p>
<p>Twitter: @<a href="https://twitter.com/m4ftm" title="@m4ftm on twitter">m4ftm</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Seeking collaboration and feedback </title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/seeking-collaboaration-and-feedback/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/seeking-collaboaration-and-feedback/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:21:08-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This project is off to a good start, but could really benefit from input from other people with more diverse experience. I am open to a variety of levels of engagement from proof-reader to co-admin. In particular some "peer review" would be helpful regarding the content. I tried my best to include all the main kinds of sex I have seen mentioned on websites and apps, but some of them I am much less familiar with that others, so I just did my best. If you have insight into any of the following, which I'm especially weak on, I'd love to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>This project is off to a good start, but could really benefit from input from other people with more diverse experience. </p>
<p id="mcetoc_1dl0d55d90">I am open to a variety of levels of engagement from proof-reader to co-admin.</p>
<p>In particular some "peer review" would be helpful regarding the content. I tried my best to include all the main kinds of sex I have seen mentioned on websites and apps, but some of them I am much less familiar with that others, so I just did my best. If you have insight into any of the following, which I'm especially weak on, I'd love to hear from you:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/bottoming-to-a-trans-guy/">Topping</a> <em>as</em> a trans man, especially <a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/getting-fucked-in-the-ass-by-a-trans-man/">strap ons</a> and <a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/sucking-a-trans-mans-dick/">bjs</a></li>
<li>Bottoming <em>to</em> a trans man in any capacity</li>
<li>Anything from cis guys that I can't notice because of my perspective</li>
</ul>
<p>If there is anything I straight up missed I'd also like to know about it. With a couple of exceptions for completeness, I am trying to limit this <em>only</em> to acts where there might conceivably be a knowledge gap. I also decided not to go for every fetish under the sun, although there is a special page about <a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/kinky-sex-with-trans-guys/">kinky sex</a> (am I missing anything there?), again not all of which I have experience with.</p>
<p>If you are interested in collaborating, here are some things that need to be done</p>
<ul>
<li>Write content</li>
<li>Edit, proofread etc</li>
<li>Provide feedback on content (peer review), brainstorm ideas for writing</li>
<li>Make existing content more interesting by finding and adding images, videos, links etc</li>
<li>Manage social media and promotion</li>
<li>Translation</li>
<li>Create other kinds of content: videos, art, podcast etc</li>
</ul>
<p>See <a href="http://m4ftm.com/about-m4ftm/m4ftm-to-do-list/">m4ftm To Do List</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Site To Do List</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/site-to-do-list/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/site-to-do-list/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:21:08-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    This site has been getting some really good feedback and the ideas are being integrated. Here is a summary of specific thingsthat are planned.A page about language, particularly with regards to body parts. Eg cock vs clit. I have most of a draft about this in progress. It will be called "talking dirty to trans men" (Suggested by basically everyone who sent feedback)Something about binders. Not sure where this will fit yet.Page about homologus anatomy, started but not adequate. Hoping for assistance on this.Update the page on genderqueers and other IDs. I am not the right person to do this, so&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0d4bl20">This site has been getting some really good feedback and the ideas are being integrated. Here is a summary of specific thingsthat are planned.</p>
<ul>
<li>A page about language, particularly with regards to body parts. Eg cock vs clit. I have most of a draft about this in progress. It will be called "talking dirty to trans men" (Suggested by basically everyone who sent feedback)</li>
<li>Something about binders. Not sure where this will fit yet.</li>
<li>Page about homologus anatomy, started but not adequate. Hoping for assistance on this.</li>
<li>Update the page on genderqueers and other IDs. I am not the right person to do this, so I await assistance.</li>
<li>Orgasms: what they are, what they look like. Not started, currently gathering feedback and ideas.</li>
<li>It seems like talking more about men who've had surgeries to their junk might be in order, but I don't know much about this, so I await assistance.</li>
<li>Sites to link to: <a href="http://transfagssexjournals.blogspot.ca/">Trans fag sex journals</a></li>
</ul>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
