<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>m4ftm</title>
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm" />
    <updated>2019-09-17T16:33:06-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>ItsExtra</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm</id>

    <entry>
        <title>ask-a-question</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/ask-a-question.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/ask-a-question.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0coqj30">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0coqj30">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

<p><strong>Have a question? Ask it here and I will answer it!</strong></p>
<p>Previous questions can be read <a href="http://m4ftm.com/category/questions-from-gay-men/">here</a>.</p>
<p>[contact-form]<br> [contact-field label="Name" type="name" required="true" /]<br> [contact-field label="Email" type="email" required="true" /]<br> [contact-field label="Website" type="url" /]<br> [contact-field label="Comment" type="textarea" required="true" /]<br> [/contact-form]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>basicsmale-and-female-bodies-Male-and-female-bodies-What8217s-the-difference</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/basicsmale-and-female-bodies-male-and-female-bodies-what8217s-the-difference.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/basicsmale-and-female-bodies-male-and-female-bodies-what8217s-the-difference.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cogvm0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cogvm0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

<p><strong>How we all began</strong></p>
<p>All fetuses start out with the same anatomy, but at <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sexual_differentiation_in_humans">7 weeks</a>, changes in anatomy start happening which lead most people to have what we think of as male and female bodies.</p>
<p>It's important to note that an <a href="http://www.isna.org/faq/frequency">estimated</a> 1% of people have "bodies [that] differ from standard male or female," and 1 in 1,666 people do not have XX (generally associated with females) or XY (thought of as male) chromosomes. Many people who have other chromosome combinations don't even know it, and may be surprised to find this out when they undergo genetic testing for some other reason. I am going to use the terms "male" and "female" here to describe the 99% of people who have bodies that meet the common definitions.</p>
<p>Male and female bodies are not as different as you may think. Everyone has basically the same structures, but they develop differently.</p>
<p><strong>Junk</strong></p>
<p>Here are two really good pictures from <em>A New View of a Woman's Body</em> that show things well (click to make them bigger):</p>
<p><a href="http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis.png"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-42" src="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/media/posts/16/nvpenis.png" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px" srcset="http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis.png 1725w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis-150x150.png 150w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis-300x300.png 300w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis-768x765.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis-1024x1020.png 1024w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvpenis-1568x1563.png 1568w" alt="NVpenis" width="300" height="299"><img class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-43" src="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/media/posts/16/nvclitoris.png" sizes="(max-width: 249px) 100vw, 249px" srcset="http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvclitoris.png 1608w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvclitoris-249x300.png 249w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvclitoris-768x927.png 768w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvclitoris-848x1024.png 848w, http://localhost:8888/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/nvclitoris-1568x1893.png 1568w" alt="NVclitoris" width="249" height="300"></a></p>
<p>You can think of a female body as having a penis that is smaller and held against the body, rather than big and hanging out. Female bodies have the same structure of erectile tissue as male bodies, but when females get turned on and hard it's not as noticeable because it hugs the body.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Wikipedia has a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_related_male_and_female_reproductive_organs">detailed list</a> of related male and female body parts. But to help you imagine what it feels like to have a female body, here are the basics (not 100% technically accurate but it gets the point across):</p>
<p>Head of penis = clitoris</p>
<p>Foreskin = hood of clitoris</p>
<p>Shaft of penis = erectile tissue under lips</p>
<p>Balls = ovaries</p>
<p>Ball sack = outer lips</p>
<p>Prostate = G Spot</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/contact.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/contact.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    tbd
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                tbd
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>talking-dirty-with-a-trans-guy-draft</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/talking-dirty-with-a-trans-guy-draft.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/talking-dirty-with-a-trans-guy-draft.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cprac0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cprac0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

<h1 id="mcetoc_1dl0cprac1">Talking dirty with a trans guy (draft)</h1>
<p>Communication is an important part of good sex. It's especially important when dealing with trans folks, because many of us have unusual relationships with our bodies. Making assumptions isn't a good idea about some things in particular. TO make sure everyone has a good time, here are some hints.</p>
<h1 id="mcetoc_1dl0cprac2">Body parts</h1>
<p>Some trans people are sensitive about the words used to describe their bodies. There can be an awful lot of emotional baggage there. For trans men, the safest thing is to use the same language he does, or just ask if he has a preference. Words that have a “feminine” connotation are the ones most likely to be uncool: pussy, cunt, vagina, vulva, vajayajay, clit, tits, boobs. Some trans guys use “masculine” words to describe their bodies, like cock, dick, balls, chest. Others use neutral terms like front hole or just front. Also, some trans guys might not like gendered language like “bitch” or “slut” if you are into that kind of thing. But then again, some do like all of the above. So you should ask.</p>
<p>If this feels like "walking on eggshells" to you, just consider that lots of people are annoyed or upset by certain words. If you were fucking someone and he referred to your genitals as your "peepee" or "Mr. Littlensoft", what would that do for you? (Unless you have a fetish that makes these turn-ons of course!) Some people refer to an asshole and rectum as a "shitter" but others find being reminded of defecation in the middle of screwing to be a boner killer. Clinical language like "scrotum" and "testicals" makes some feel awkward and unsexy, while others prefer it. Sometimes a certain use of language can remind a person of an ex they had a painful breakup with, or someone who treated them badly. The point is that nothing here is different from anyone else, other than having a head start on predicting things that could be problems.</p>
<p>To find out about this, you can ask direct questions like, "are there any words you don't like to describe your body?" or "what do you call your vagina?". You can also pick up from the conversation when you ask him about other things what he likes. If he mentions "stroking my dick" or "a dildo in my vagina" those would both be good signs.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cprac3">Asking about it</h2>
<p>You'll notice on this website that every page says something along the lines of "but you should probably ask him". Is that a mood killer? Does it turn hooking up into a game of 20,000 questions with an intake form and boxes to check? I don't think so.</p>
<p>Since I switched from fucking straight guys to gay guys, I have been really impressed with the communication about sex most homos are comfortable with. "What are you into?" is a ubiquitous question that's asked really early on, by most men. This is a welcome change from straight guys, many of whom don't think to ask, and who can't really give a good answer if you ask them. Seriously, ask your straight female friends how their discussions of sex have gone and compare notes.</p>
<p>That's to say, if you are a gay guy who is used to setting up sex on apps and websites, <em>you are probably already doing this</em>. Just keep doing what you've been doing. "What are you into?" is a great question, and should get you a lot of the info you want to know. "Is there anything you are really NOT into?" is a good followup.</p>
<p><strong>Trans men know themselves, and they know what they are getting into when they seek hook ups.</strong></p>
<p>They aren't going to wait for you to ask every single question possible. By the time you get to picking whose place, or which park/vehicle/bathhouse, to meet up in, they should be upfront about things that bother them if those are obvious possibilities for them. A person who, for instance, doesn't ever take off his shirt during sex and doesn't want you touching his chest (which is no uncommon), should be self-aware enough to find a moment to tell you this if you are arranging for sex in a location where this is something that would likely happen. The reason this is mentioned here is so you aren't <em>shocked</em> by this request, and it doesn't prompt you to launch into a long line of <em>very unsexy</em> questioning about his reasons.  (He might choose to share this, but an interrogation is usually not the order of the day.) You can just think, "OK, he will leave his shirt on, I'll concentrate elsewhere" <em>or</em> "nipples are the hottest and most important part of a man's body and there's no reason to bother getting together if this is off the table". If the latter, you have saved both of you a time-wasting and awkward (if not disturbing) encounter by calling it off. If the former, you are better equipped to get horned up for the hot time you <em>are</em> going to share together, thinking about other body parts.</p>
<p>Once you've narrowed things down a bit and found what your mutual interests are, you can ask more specific questions that are relevant. If he's gonna give you a no recip bj, you don't really need to know what words he likes to describe his font hole. Just don't mention it unless he does.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Vibrators</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/vibrators.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/vibrators.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0co50n0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <hr>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0co50n0">published: false<br> date: 2019-09-09T09:09:09+00:00<br> author: Jack<br> layout: page<br> title: M4FTM<br> permalink: /.html<br> categories: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> tags: ['m4ftm', 'gay']<br> excerpt_separator:</h2>

<p>Some trans men like to play with vibrat</p>
<p>For the most part, vibrators are for the outside of the body, not the inside. Some of them are specifically designed in such a way that they cannot comfortably or safely be inserted, but most can be if you want to. Ask your partner if that's something he would enjoy. But your best bet is to apply a vibe to the glans either directly or through the hood. You can try rubbing it on the labia. Vibrators are pretty personal in terms of preferences, so once again the easiest is to just ask your partner to show you what he wants.</p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who should not fuck a trans man?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/who-should-not-fuck-a-trans-man.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/who-should-not-fuck-a-trans-man.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    After all this writing about why and how to fuck trans men, I'd like to bring things down a bit and mention some situations where you should maybe reconsider, because you risk ruining someone else's day. You'd be better off with a blow up doll While some enjoy it, many trans people find it off-putting when they feel the only thing a person is interested in is their weird body. Figure out what else you like about them. While I find it weird when someone doesn't want to fuck me just cause of my junk, it's actually much weirder when that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0clqg00">After all this writing about why and how to fuck trans men, I'd like to bring things down a bit and mention some situations where you should maybe reconsider, because you risk ruining someone else's day.</p>
<p><strong>You'd be better off with a blow up doll</strong></p>
<p>While some enjoy it, many trans people find it off-putting when they feel the only thing a person is interested in is their weird body. Figure out what <em>else</em> you like about them. While I find it weird when someone doesn't want to fuck me just cause of my junk, it's actually much weirder when that is literally the <em>only</em> thing they want. Before I learned to identify these guys, I had some really bad sex.</p>
<p>Don't treat a trans person like a kinky walk on the wild side, unless that's something they're into. I bet that very few trans people enjoy being thought of us taboo or wild just because of their bodies.</p>
<p><strong>You feel like you should</strong></p>
<p>Maybe you heard about how transphobic cis (non trans) gay guys are and have decided you will do right by your community and fuck a trans person. Wasting a trans guys time so you can use him like a fleshlight, think of someone you actually want to fuck, and check something off your bucket list is not fun for the other people. I have now learned how to filter these people out after some really abysmal sex.</p>
<p><strong>You can't wait to tell your friends</strong></p>
<p>If you are hoping to hook up with a trans guy so you can show your friends how progressive you are, wait until you find someone you would have thought was attractive. If you think this is a good way to boost your social status, you probably aren't as progressive as you think you are.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>If I fuck an FTM am I still gay?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-i-fuck-an-ftm-am-i-still-gay.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-i-fuck-an-ftm-am-i-still-gay.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Do you have to be at least a little bit bi to fuck, or want to fuck a trans guy? Some gold star gays think you do. I am of course biased, but I disagree. You just have to be attracted to him, and he has to be attracted to you. Trans men are men. It's how we see ourselves and for the most part it's how other people see us. We have different stories and bodies, but so does everyone. It seems to me that gay men can have a sort of knee jerk reaction to trans men, especially&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec0">Do you have to be at least a <em>little</em> bit bi to fuck, or want to fuck a trans guy? Some gold star gays think you do.</p>
<p>I am of course biased, but I disagree. You just have to be attracted to him, and he has to be attracted to you. Trans men are men. It's how we see ourselves and for the most part it's how other people see us. We have different stories and bodies, but so does everyone.</p>
<p>It seems to me that gay men can have a sort of knee jerk reaction to trans men, especially if they had never considered the idea in relationship to their own bodies. Taking a moment to think about the concept in general, and the cute guy in front of you, might open a new door. Keep reading this website to learn more about this.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec1">Who cares?</h2>
<p>You came out as gay, so you know you are capable of standing up for your desires in the face of other people's labels. Instead of fitting your behaviour to match a label, why not behave how you feel?</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec2">Another point of view</h2>
<p>Cartoonist and gold star gay Bill Roundy drew his experiences <a href="http://comics.billroundy.com/?p=1116">in a comic</a>. Here's one panel, but you should read the whole thing if this is still troubling you.</p>
<p><a href="http://comics.billroundy.com/?p=1116"><img class="aligncenter size-custom" title="" src="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/media/posts/29/img_1931.gif" alt="" width="600" height="857"></a></p>
<p><a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ItsExtra/m4ftm/master/_media/160222-1400x2006-1024x146.png">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ItsExtra/m4ftm/master/_media/160222-1400x2006-1024x146.png</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>If you want to fuck men, why didn&#x27;t you just stay a woman?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-you-want-to-fuck-men-why-didnt-you-just-stay-a-woman.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-you-want-to-fuck-men-why-didnt-you-just-stay-a-woman.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It certainly was easier to get cock. I was a pretty, smart young woman who had the sex brain of a gay guy. It turns out that straight guys love women who think and fuck like men. But otherwise, it wasn't working out for me.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0ce3on0">It certainly was easier to get cock. I was a pretty, smart young woman who had the sex brain of a gay guy. It turns out that straight guys <em>love</em> women who think and fuck like men.</p>
<p>But otherwise, it wasn't working out for me.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What if I say something wrong?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/what-if-i-say-something-wrong.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/what-if-i-say-something-wrong.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Here are some tips for getting along with trans people you fuck. Having control over who knows a person is trans is very important to some of us. There are many reasons for this, but at the end of the day a person’s health information is private. Some ways you could accidentally upset someone: If you think you might need to tell anyone, including your boyfriend or your BFF, about a trans person’s status for any reason (even if it’s just to tell them how goddamned smokin hot the sex was), you should mention it to him and find out what his boundaries are.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp0">Here are some tips for getting along with trans people you fuck.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp1">Privacy</h2>
<p>Having control over who knows a person is trans is very important to some of us. There are many reasons for this, but at the end of the day a person’s health information is private. Some ways you could accidentally upset someone:</p>
<ul>
<li>Referring to someone as “my trans friend” or something like that</li>
<li>Revealing a past name to someone who didn’t know it (this is called <a href="http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=deadname">deadnaming</a>)</li>
<li>Telling all your friends you dated or hooked up with a trans guy, who they will later meet and be able to figure it out</li>
</ul>
<p>If you think you might need to tell anyone, including your boyfriend or your BFF, about a trans person’s status for any reason (even if it’s just to tell them how goddamned smokin hot the sex was), you should mention it to him and find out what his boundaries are. He will probably understand that you just can’t keep quiet, but might ask that you keep the information away from certain people or groups, like someone who is connected to their job, or who is shitty some how. Or he might not care. Some trans people are completely open about their health history.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp2">But don’t go into the closet yourself</h2>
<p>And don’t drag him in there with you. If you are seeing someone who is known in your social circles to be trans, don’t be embarrassed about it. Don’t hide that fact. It is a real bummer to feel like you are a shameful secret. It’s like straight men who date big women but don’t want their friends to know, Its just shitty. Man up.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp3">The gay closet vs trans privacy</h2>
<p>Being “out” about being trans is different than being “out” about being gay. Being out as gay is about your social, economic, familial, sexual and political relationships. These art part of a person’s public life, their place in the collective, which are difficult and uncomfortable to separate.</p>
<p>Being trans though, is a private thing. It is about how we relate to ourselves, and how we want people to relate to us. Trans people spend a lot of time, money and frequently take great personal risks and losses to get ourselves to the right place, to be seen the way we want. Some of us don’t want that part of our story preceding us. It’s intimate.</p>
<p>Some people are “out” in some parts of their life but not others. If you don’t know for a fact that a trans person is comfortable with their status known but someone else, don’t share.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp4">Things you shouldn’t say or ask</h2>
<p>Here are some things that most trans people will find rude or icky. If you need more explanation, see GLAAD’s <a href="http://www.glaad.org/transgender/allies">Tips for allies of transgender people</a>.</p>
<ul>
<li>“What is you real/birth/old/legal <strong>name</strong>?”</li>
<li>“Can I see a <strong>photo</strong> of you before you transitioned?”</li>
<li>“You look <strong>just like</strong> a man!” “I couldn’t even <strong>tell</strong> you were trans.”</li>
<li>“Have you had the <strong>surgery</strong>?” (read more <a href="https://m4ftm.com/basics/what-is-transition/">about transition</a> to learn why this question doesn’t make any sense)</li>
<li>If you aren’t in a context where you need to know, like because you are thinking of hooking up, and he’s not asking you about your junk, <strong>don’t ask him</strong> about his bodies, health history or other private business</li>
<li>Try not to make <strong>assumptions</strong> about his mental health, history, or struggles</li>
<li>“Your so <strong>brave</strong>“, “I could never be so strong” “I admire you” these are nice things to say to someone, but not <em>just</em> because they are trans</li>
<li>Don’t assume he is “<strong>trapped</strong> in a woman’s body,” or “<strong>hates</strong> his body” that’s not something everyone (or even many people) feel</li>
<li>Anything about “<strong>best of both worlds</strong>“—I don’t know if this universal, but I personally find this extremely off-putting</li>
<li>If you don’t know someone well enough to be 100% sure they are OK with it, avoid questions about our <strong>personal history</strong> as it relates to gender, “did you always feel different from the other kids?” “did you ever try to kill yourself?” “when did you know you were trans?”</li>
<li>Which <strong>bathroom</strong> do you use?</li>
<li>How do you <strong>piss</strong>? (Acceptable if you are looking for some <a href="https://m4ftm.com/how-do-you-fuck-a-trans-guy/kinky-sex-with-trans-guys/">water sports</a>!)</li>
</ul>
<p>If you aren’t sure if something is OK to ask or say, try to think of another thing that would be the same level of intrusiveness, intimacy on another issue. If you just met someone you know to be trans and are curious about their medical history or surgical status, imagine if you just met someone you know has children. Do you ask them how the birth went? Was it vaginal or C-section? Was an epidural used? What the copulation passionate or perfunctory? Unless you are in a situation where that’s topical, like a new mother’s group, or someone you are already really close with, it would be considered rude. So if you are on a hookup site, you can ask about someone’s body, because everyone is asking each other about their bodies. But if you are at your niece’s 5th birthday party and a trans neighbour comes by for a piece of cake, you’ll just have hold your questions.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp5">If you make a mistake</h2>
<p>Nobody’s perfect. I have mispronouned (using “she” instead of “he” when for some reason referring to myself in the third person) <em>myself</em> out of habit. Just apologize, move on and don't do it again.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp6">The word tranny</h2>
<p>Tranny is a word you should not use. Some people have reclaimed it, but just like you probably don’t like being called faggot by straight people, you shouldn’t use reclaimed words if you are not a member of the target group. Also, it is a word that has historically been used to describe trans women, often in the context of extreme violence, so if you ask me, trans men have no business “reclaiming” it. Unless you are a trans woman you should wash the word from your vocabulary.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp7">Conclusion</h2>
<p>Trans men and other trans people are just people and we want to be treated the same way other people are.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Where can I find FTM porn?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-can-i-find-ftm-porn.html"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-can-i-find-ftm-porn.html</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Tumblr is full of hot gay FTMs doing all sorts of dirty nasty things. To get you started: You can search for amateur porn on websites like Xtube, Pornhunb,GayMaleTube, Xnxx or wherever you like to go. FTM Fucker “FTM porn featuring the hottest trans men by director James Darling” Bonus Hole Boys “the web’s hottest hardcore gay FTM porn exclusively featuring trans men and cis men fucking. FTM porn star Cyd St. Vincent seeks out the horniest men built with an extra hole to play out their fantasies of cruising, daddy/boy play, bondage, raw sex, gangbangs and roleplays with hot pumping, cock sucking,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m0">Tumblr is full of hot gay FTMs doing all sorts of dirty nasty things. To get you started:</p>
<ul>
<li><del><a href="http://transexy.tumblr.com/">My trans body / transexy</a></del></li>
<li><del><a href="http://gayftmpornblr.tumblr.com/">Gay FTM porn</a></del></li>
<li><del><a href="http://ftmgayporn.tumblr.com/">FTM Gay porn</a></del></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m1">Amateur FTM porn</h2>
<p>You can search for amateur porn on websites like <a href="http://www.xtube.com/search/video/100052561-ftm-gay">Xtube</a>, <a href="http://www.pornhub.com/gay/video/search?search=ftm">Pornhunb</a>,<a href="http://www.gaymaletube.com/search/gay+ftm/">GayMaleTube</a>, <a href="http://www.xnxx.com/?k=gay+ftm">Xnxx</a> or wherever you like to go.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m2">Professional FTM porn</h2>
<p><a href="http://ftmfucker.com/gay-ftm-porn/">FTM Fucker</a> “FTM porn featuring the hottest trans men by director James Darling”</p>
<p><a href="http://bonusholeboys.com/site/">Bonus Hole Boys</a> “the web’s hottest hardcore gay FTM porn exclusively featuring trans men and cis men fucking. FTM porn star Cyd St. Vincent seeks out the horniest men built with an extra hole to play out their fantasies of cruising, daddy/boy play, bondage, raw sex, gangbangs and roleplays with hot pumping, cock sucking, rimming, edging, BDSM, double-penetration, ejaculation, and fisting.”</p>
<p>A Manhunt daily article, <a href="http://manhuntdaily.com/2015/02/the-cock-buffet-brought-to-you-by-ridiculously-hot-ftm-guys/">The cock buffet: Brought to you by ridiculously hot FTM guys</a> has links to several FTM porn models.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
