<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>m4ftm</title>
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm" />
    <updated>2019-09-17T17:39:00-04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>ItsExtra</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Contact</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/contact/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/contact/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    tbd
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                tbd
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Who should not fuck a trans man?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/who-should-not-fuck-a-trans-man/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/who-should-not-fuck-a-trans-man/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:25:26-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    After all this writing about why and how to fuck trans men, I'd like to bring things down a bit and mention some situations where you should maybe reconsider, because you risk ruining someone else's day. You'd be better off with a blow up doll While some enjoy it, many trans people find it off-putting when they feel the only thing a person is interested in is their weird body. Figure out what else you like about them. While I find it weird when someone doesn't want to fuck me just cause of my junk, it's actually much weirder when that&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0clqg00">After all this writing about why and how to fuck trans men, I'd like to bring things down a bit and mention some situations where you should maybe reconsider, because you risk ruining someone else's day.</p>
<p><strong>You'd be better off with a blow up doll</strong></p>
<p>While some enjoy it, many trans people find it off-putting when they feel the only thing a person is interested in is their weird body. Figure out what <em>else</em> you like about them. While I find it weird when someone doesn't want to fuck me just cause of my junk, it's actually much weirder when that is literally the <em>only</em> thing they want. Before I learned to identify these guys, I had some really bad sex.</p>
<p>Don't treat a trans person like a kinky walk on the wild side, unless that's something they're into. I bet that very few trans people enjoy being thought of us taboo or wild just because of their bodies.</p>
<p><strong>You feel like you should</strong></p>
<p>Maybe you heard about how transphobic cis (non trans) gay guys are and have decided you will do right by your community and fuck a trans person. Wasting a trans guys time so you can use him like a fleshlight, think of someone you actually want to fuck, and check something off your bucket list is not fun for the other people. I have now learned how to filter these people out after some really abysmal sex.</p>
<p><strong>You can't wait to tell your friends</strong></p>
<p>If you are hoping to hook up with a trans guy so you can show your friends how progressive you are, wait until you find someone you would have thought was attractive. If you think this is a good way to boost your social status, you probably aren't as progressive as you think you are.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>If I fuck an FTM am I still gay?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-i-fuck-an-ftm-am-i-still-gay/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-i-fuck-an-ftm-am-i-still-gay/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Do you have to be at least a little bit bi to fuck, or want to fuck a trans guy? Some gold star gays think you do. I am of course biased, but I disagree. You just have to be attracted to him, and he has to be attracted to you. Trans men are men. It's how we see ourselves and for the most part it's how other people see us. We have different stories and bodies, but so does everyone. It seems to me that gay men can have a sort of knee jerk reaction to trans men, especially&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec0">Do you have to be at least a <em>little</em> bit bi to fuck, or want to fuck a trans guy? Some gold star gays think you do.</p>
<p>I am of course biased, but I disagree. You just have to be attracted to him, and he has to be attracted to you. Trans men are men. It's how we see ourselves and for the most part it's how other people see us. We have different stories and bodies, but so does everyone.</p>
<p>It seems to me that gay men can have a sort of knee jerk reaction to trans men, especially if they had never considered the idea in relationship to their own bodies. Taking a moment to think about the concept in general, and the cute guy in front of you, might open a new door. Keep reading this website to learn more about this.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec1">Who cares?</h2>
<p>You came out as gay, so you know you are capable of standing up for your desires in the face of other people's labels. Instead of fitting your behaviour to match a label, why not behave how you feel?</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0ceuec2">Another point of view</h2>
<p>Cartoonist and gold star gay Bill Roundy drew his experiences <a href="http://comics.billroundy.com/?p=1116">in a comic</a>. Here's one panel, but you should read the whole thing if this is still troubling you.</p>
<p><a href="http://comics.billroundy.com/?p=1116"><img class="aligncenter size-custom" title="" src="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/media/posts/29/img_1931.gif" alt="" width="600" height="857"></a></p>
<p><a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ItsExtra/m4ftm/master/_media/160222-1400x2006-1024x146.png">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ItsExtra/m4ftm/master/_media/160222-1400x2006-1024x146.png</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>If you want to fuck men, why didn&#x27;t you just stay a woman?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-you-want-to-fuck-men-why-didnt-you-just-stay-a-woman/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/if-you-want-to-fuck-men-why-didnt-you-just-stay-a-woman/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It certainly was easier to get cock. I was a pretty, smart young woman who had the sex brain of a gay guy. It turns out that straight guys love women who think and fuck like men. But otherwise, it wasn't working out for me.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0ce3on0">It certainly was easier to get cock. I was a pretty, smart young woman who had the sex brain of a gay guy. It turns out that straight guys <em>love</em> women who think and fuck like men.</p>
<p>But otherwise, it wasn't working out for me.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>What if I say something wrong?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/what-if-i-say-something-wrong/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/what-if-i-say-something-wrong/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Here are some tips for getting along with trans people you fuck. Having control over who knows a person is trans is very important to some of us. There are many reasons for this, but at the end of the day a person’s health information is private. Some ways you could accidentally upset someone: If you think you might need to tell anyone, including your boyfriend or your BFF, about a trans person’s status for any reason (even if it’s just to tell them how goddamned smokin hot the sex was), you should mention it to him and find out what his boundaries are.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp0">Here are some tips for getting along with trans people you fuck.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp1">Privacy</h2>
<p>Having control over who knows a person is trans is very important to some of us. There are many reasons for this, but at the end of the day a person’s health information is private. Some ways you could accidentally upset someone:</p>
<ul>
<li>Referring to someone as “my trans friend” or something like that</li>
<li>Revealing a past name to someone who didn’t know it (this is called <a href="http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=deadname">deadnaming</a>)</li>
<li>Telling all your friends you dated or hooked up with a trans guy, who they will later meet and be able to figure it out</li>
</ul>
<p>If you think you might need to tell anyone, including your boyfriend or your BFF, about a trans person’s status for any reason (even if it’s just to tell them how goddamned smokin hot the sex was), you should mention it to him and find out what his boundaries are. He will probably understand that you just can’t keep quiet, but might ask that you keep the information away from certain people or groups, like someone who is connected to their job, or who is shitty some how. Or he might not care. Some trans people are completely open about their health history.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp2">But don’t go into the closet yourself</h2>
<p>And don’t drag him in there with you. If you are seeing someone who is known in your social circles to be trans, don’t be embarrassed about it. Don’t hide that fact. It is a real bummer to feel like you are a shameful secret. It’s like straight men who date big women but don’t want their friends to know, Its just shitty. Man up.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp3">The gay closet vs trans privacy</h2>
<p>Being “out” about being trans is different than being “out” about being gay. Being out as gay is about your social, economic, familial, sexual and political relationships. These art part of a person’s public life, their place in the collective, which are difficult and uncomfortable to separate.</p>
<p>Being trans though, is a private thing. It is about how we relate to ourselves, and how we want people to relate to us. Trans people spend a lot of time, money and frequently take great personal risks and losses to get ourselves to the right place, to be seen the way we want. Some of us don’t want that part of our story preceding us. It’s intimate.</p>
<p>Some people are “out” in some parts of their life but not others. If you don’t know for a fact that a trans person is comfortable with their status known but someone else, don’t share.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp4">Things you shouldn’t say or ask</h2>
<p>Here are some things that most trans people will find rude or icky. If you need more explanation, see GLAAD’s <a href="http://www.glaad.org/transgender/allies">Tips for allies of transgender people</a>.</p>
<ul>
<li>“What is you real/birth/old/legal <strong>name</strong>?”</li>
<li>“Can I see a <strong>photo</strong> of you before you transitioned?”</li>
<li>“You look <strong>just like</strong> a man!” “I couldn’t even <strong>tell</strong> you were trans.”</li>
<li>“Have you had the <strong>surgery</strong>?” (read more <a href="https://m4ftm.com/basics/what-is-transition/">about transition</a> to learn why this question doesn’t make any sense)</li>
<li>If you aren’t in a context where you need to know, like because you are thinking of hooking up, and he’s not asking you about your junk, <strong>don’t ask him</strong> about his bodies, health history or other private business</li>
<li>Try not to make <strong>assumptions</strong> about his mental health, history, or struggles</li>
<li>“Your so <strong>brave</strong>“, “I could never be so strong” “I admire you” these are nice things to say to someone, but not <em>just</em> because they are trans</li>
<li>Don’t assume he is “<strong>trapped</strong> in a woman’s body,” or “<strong>hates</strong> his body” that’s not something everyone (or even many people) feel</li>
<li>Anything about “<strong>best of both worlds</strong>“—I don’t know if this universal, but I personally find this extremely off-putting</li>
<li>If you don’t know someone well enough to be 100% sure they are OK with it, avoid questions about our <strong>personal history</strong> as it relates to gender, “did you always feel different from the other kids?” “did you ever try to kill yourself?” “when did you know you were trans?”</li>
<li>Which <strong>bathroom</strong> do you use?</li>
<li>How do you <strong>piss</strong>? (Acceptable if you are looking for some <a href="https://m4ftm.com/how-do-you-fuck-a-trans-guy/kinky-sex-with-trans-guys/">water sports</a>!)</li>
</ul>
<p>If you aren’t sure if something is OK to ask or say, try to think of another thing that would be the same level of intrusiveness, intimacy on another issue. If you just met someone you know to be trans and are curious about their medical history or surgical status, imagine if you just met someone you know has children. Do you ask them how the birth went? Was it vaginal or C-section? Was an epidural used? What the copulation passionate or perfunctory? Unless you are in a situation where that’s topical, like a new mother’s group, or someone you are already really close with, it would be considered rude. So if you are on a hookup site, you can ask about someone’s body, because everyone is asking each other about their bodies. But if you are at your niece’s 5th birthday party and a trans neighbour comes by for a piece of cake, you’ll just have hold your questions.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp5">If you make a mistake</h2>
<p>Nobody’s perfect. I have mispronouned (using “she” instead of “he” when for some reason referring to myself in the third person) <em>myself</em> out of habit. Just apologize, move on and don't do it again.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp6">The word tranny</h2>
<p>Tranny is a word you should not use. Some people have reclaimed it, but just like you probably don’t like being called faggot by straight people, you shouldn’t use reclaimed words if you are not a member of the target group. Also, it is a word that has historically been used to describe trans women, often in the context of extreme violence, so if you ask me, trans men have no business “reclaiming” it. Unless you are a trans woman you should wash the word from your vocabulary.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cd8jp7">Conclusion</h2>
<p>Trans men and other trans people are just people and we want to be treated the same way other people are.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Where can I find FTM porn?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-can-i-find-ftm-porn/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-can-i-find-ftm-porn/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Tumblr is full of hot gay FTMs doing all sorts of dirty nasty things. To get you started: You can search for amateur porn on websites like Xtube, Pornhunb,GayMaleTube, Xnxx or wherever you like to go. FTM Fucker “FTM porn featuring the hottest trans men by director James Darling” Bonus Hole Boys “the web’s hottest hardcore gay FTM porn exclusively featuring trans men and cis men fucking. FTM porn star Cyd St. Vincent seeks out the horniest men built with an extra hole to play out their fantasies of cruising, daddy/boy play, bondage, raw sex, gangbangs and roleplays with hot pumping, cock sucking,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m0">Tumblr is full of hot gay FTMs doing all sorts of dirty nasty things. To get you started:</p>
<ul>
<li><del><a href="http://transexy.tumblr.com/">My trans body / transexy</a></del></li>
<li><del><a href="http://gayftmpornblr.tumblr.com/">Gay FTM porn</a></del></li>
<li><del><a href="http://ftmgayporn.tumblr.com/">FTM Gay porn</a></del></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m1">Amateur FTM porn</h2>
<p>You can search for amateur porn on websites like <a href="http://www.xtube.com/search/video/100052561-ftm-gay">Xtube</a>, <a href="http://www.pornhub.com/gay/video/search?search=ftm">Pornhunb</a>,<a href="http://www.gaymaletube.com/search/gay+ftm/">GayMaleTube</a>, <a href="http://www.xnxx.com/?k=gay+ftm">Xnxx</a> or wherever you like to go.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0cc92m2">Professional FTM porn</h2>
<p><a href="http://ftmfucker.com/gay-ftm-porn/">FTM Fucker</a> “FTM porn featuring the hottest trans men by director James Darling”</p>
<p><a href="http://bonusholeboys.com/site/">Bonus Hole Boys</a> “the web’s hottest hardcore gay FTM porn exclusively featuring trans men and cis men fucking. FTM porn star Cyd St. Vincent seeks out the horniest men built with an extra hole to play out their fantasies of cruising, daddy/boy play, bondage, raw sex, gangbangs and roleplays with hot pumping, cock sucking, rimming, edging, BDSM, double-penetration, ejaculation, and fisting.”</p>
<p>A Manhunt daily article, <a href="http://manhuntdaily.com/2015/02/the-cock-buffet-brought-to-you-by-ridiculously-hot-ftm-guys/">The cock buffet: Brought to you by ridiculously hot FTM guys</a> has links to several FTM porn models.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Where do I find FTMs to hook up with?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-do-i-find-ftms-to-hook-up-with/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/where-do-i-find-ftms-to-hook-up-with/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    If all this sounds like a good time to you, and you don’t have a specific person in mind, you can go about finding trans men to hook up with the same way you find anyone else. Whatever apps or cruising sites are popular in your area can have trans men. There are more trans folks in places than others. Not all trans men state their status on their profiles. Being trans is a private fact for some people, and for various reasons they don’t want to put the info with their picture or other info. Others have their trans&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0caqh20">If all this sounds like a good time to you, and you don’t have a specific person in mind, you can go about finding trans men to hook up with the same way you find anyone else. Whatever apps or cruising sites are popular in your area can have trans men. There are more trans folks in places than others.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0caqh21">Identify yourself as friendly</h2>
<p>Not all trans men state their status on their profiles. Being trans is a private fact for some people, and for various reasons they don’t want to put the info with their picture or other info. Others have their trans status prominently displayed and in some contexts may tell you some of the historical/medical stuff you want to know to get with them right on the profile. Some trans men will drop hints in their profiles by saying things like “I’m not your typical guy” which of course could be referring to something else.</p>
<p>If you are open to encounters with trans guys, put something like “ftm friendly” or “trans positive” in your profile. It will be noticed. I honestly think this is the best strategy. Try the passive route for a while before becoming more aggressive in your search, because it’s easy to rub people the wrong way.</p>
<p>Putting notes like that on your profile also shows other guys that you are not embarrassed to fuck trans men, which helps change the atmosphere in the gay and MSM communities to one which is more friendly towards us.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0caqh22">Meeting in person</h2>
<p>In some big cities (maybe even some smaller ones) there are places you can go where you stand a better chance of meeting a trans guy. Some gay/lesbian bars have regular trans fag nights. There also might be certain bars which are known to be friendly to trans men where you are more likely to find them. There are also branches and other sort of meet-up groups. <a href="http://fetlife.com/">Fetlife</a> is a good place to look (you’ll need an account).</p>
<p>If you do decide to actively look for trans guys, don’t be a fucking weirdo about it. Play it cool. Don’t fuck a trans man if there is <a href="https://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/reasons-to-not-fuck-an-ftm/">a reason you shouldn’t be</a>. Even if you are a fabulous person who is definitely not a creeper, be aware that there are a lot of creepers hanging around some of these places, and folks might have their back up. Don’t take it personally. Try to take any constructive feedback you get and apply it to your future behaviour.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0caqh23">Apps and websites</h2>
<ul>
<li>Adam4Adam</li>
<li>Scruff</li>
<li>Grindr</li>
<li>Dudesnude</li>
<li>Recon (fetish)</li>
<li>Manhunt</li>
<li><del>Craigslist</del></li>
<li>Fetlife (“the facebook of sex”)</li>
<li>OkCupid (more of a dating website)</li>
</ul>
<p>Tinder has <a href="http://www.advocate.com/politics/transgender/2015/06/05/tinder-allegedly-banning-transgender-users-because-theyre-trans">gone out of its way</a> to deny service to trans people so trans guys may either be unable to use it or unwilling. You might find some there though.</p>
<h2 id="mcetoc_1dl0caqh24">Outside links</h2>
<p><a href="http://charlesasher.blogspot.ca/2012/08/ftm-dating-sites.html">FTM dating sites</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why would anyone choose to be gay?</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/why-would-anyone-choose-to-be-gay/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/why-would-anyone-choose-to-be-gay/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:23:32-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    It makes me sad to hear this, especially when it comes from men who seem to be otherwise "out and proud." The kernel of self-loathing which is the foundation of this question is evident. It's basically saying (and I've heard this said aloud too) "I would never, ever choose to be gay, but since I am I will make the best of it." I do not think homosexuality and gender diversity are defects, I think they are part of the natural variance in humans and the vast majority of the animal kingdom. I like being gay. I knew I was going to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0c7a9l0">It makes me sad to hear this, especially when it comes from men who seem to be otherwise "out and proud." The kernel of self-loathing which is the foundation of this question is evident. It's basically saying (and I've heard this said aloud too) "I would never, ever choose to be gay, but since I am I will make the best of it."</p>
<p>I do not think homosexuality and gender diversity are defects, I think they are part of the natural variance in humans and the vast majority of the animal kingdom.</p>
<p>I like being gay. I knew I was going to be gay many years before I understood how transition worked, and that I could be a man. When I was a kid, I was really puzzled why I wasn't attracted to girls. I actually tried pretty hard. I felt I should be. Gay. I was gay. But  I wasn't even a little bit bisexual. I kept thinking of myself as gay. I had the gayest sex I could with the str8 boys available to me. I loved bi guys, that felt much more legit.</p>
<p>Now I get to be gay, which is wonderful in some ways, although it can be lonely at times</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Bottoming to a trans guy 101</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/bottoming-to-a-trans-guy/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/bottoming-to-a-trans-guy/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:22:56-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Lots of trans men enjoy topping. Some guys might have had some sort of surgery which allows them to put their dick into your hungry hole. For those who don't, there are all kinds of ways for them to fuck you: Other than that, he can use fingers and hands (gloves are always a good idea) or other objects to open you up. He might also like a rim job.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0criju0">Lots of trans men enjoy topping.</p>
<p>Some guys might have had some sort of surgery which allows them to put their dick into your hungry hole. For those who don't, there are all kinds of ways for them to fuck you:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/getting-fucked-in-the-ass-by-a-trans-man/">Getting fucked in the ass by a trans man's cock</a></li>
<li><a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/sucking-a-trans-mans-dick/">Sucking off a trans man</a></li>
<li><a href="http://m4ftm.com/hooking-up/jerking-off-a-trans-guy/">Jerking off a trans guy's cock</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Other than that, he can use fingers and hands (gloves are always a good idea) or other objects to open you up. He might also like a rim job.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Fingering a trans guy&#x27;s front hole</title>
        <author>
            <name>ItsExtra</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/fingering-a-trans-guys-front-hole/"/>
        <id>https://itsextra.github.io/m4ftm/fingering-a-trans-guys-front-hole/</id>

        <updated>2019-09-17T19:22:56-04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    If someone wants you to put your fingers in his front hole, make sure you have nice short nails without sharp bits, clean hands and lubricant. Front holes and back holes have different muscles, with the front lacking the sphincter muscles that can be pulled closed tight on sure people. While a lot of people need slow warm up for anal sex starting with one finger and working up, this might not be necessary for a pussy. You can probably go to two fingers quickly if not right away. A lot of guys assume that the best thing to do&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p id="mcetoc_1dl0cqomf0">If someone wants you to put your fingers in his front hole, make sure you have nice short nails without sharp bits, clean hands and lubricant. Front holes and back holes have different muscles, with the front lacking the sphincter muscles that can be pulled closed tight on sure people. While a lot of people need slow warm up for anal sex starting with one finger and working up, this might not be necessary for a pussy. You can probably go to two fingers quickly if not right away.</p>
<p>A lot of guys assume that the best thing to do is imitate a penis, and start jack hammering in and out. While jackhammers have their place, you'll have better luck trying to hit the "G spot". Like the prostate, the G spot is located two or three inches inside toward the front. You might not actually feel anything special. But you will be able to tell if you found the right spot from your partner's reaction. If this is something they enjoy, they can help you fingerbang them just right.</p>
<p>The easiest way to find the G spot is to have your partner lie or sit with his legs open and knees bent. Face each other and put your index and middle finger inside him (your palm is facing up) Then move your fingers inside him like you were signalling to someone to "come here." Adjust the angle, speed and pressure while you listen, watch and feel his reactions. This position will let you use the thumb of the same hand to rub his cock head too. You can also have him touch himself, or someone can use a vibrator at the same time.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
